mzansixxx.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Mzansixxx

**Please read this privacy policy carefully, as your access to and use of our Website signifies that you have read, understand and agree to all terms within this privacy policy. If you do not agree with any part of this privacy policy or our terms, please do not access or continue to use our Website or otherwise submit your personal data. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data  ** **If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please see “Contact Information” below for information on how to contact us.  ** **This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which  mzansixxx.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the **[**mzansixxx.com**](https://www.mzansixxx.com/) **  website.**

###  **Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.  

###  **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

###  **Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. **How we use collected information**

mzansixxx.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  1.  **To improve customer service** - Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  2.  **  To personalize user experience **- ** ** We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  

  3.  _ _ **To improve our Site** - We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  

  4.  **  To send periodic emails **- We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

###  **How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, **username,** **password,** **transaction information and data stored on our Site.**

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a **SSL secured** communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with **PCI vulnerability** standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

###  **Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

###  **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

###  **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.  

###  **Compliance with children's online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18. If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) If we become aware that a minor has provided us with Personal Information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate that person’s account  

###  **Changes to this privacy policy**

mzansixxx.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

###  **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms](https://www.mzansixxx.com/static/terms) of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.  

###  **Contacting us:**

 **If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact**[ **Here**](https://www.mzansixxx.com/feedback) **  or Drop and E-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**

###  **GDPR (General Data Protecton Regulation)**

 **In accordance with the General Data Protecton Regulation law in the European Union effective May 25, 2018, Mzansixxx.com users can request a copy of their personal data as well as get Pornhub to delete their personal data. You can request a copy of your person data or have your data deleted**[ **here**](https://www.mzansixxx.com/feedback)
